Mikalai Kisialiou

Fullstack Web Developer



Contact

Location:

Yerevan, Armenia

Phone:

+374 94 880 567

Email:

korn9509@gmail.com

Portfolio:

nickkiselev.me

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/nick-kiselev/

GitHub:

github.com/tectonick

Languages

English – Upper-Intermediate Russian – Native

Main Skills





Summary

An enthusiastic and highly motivated **Fullstack Software Developer**. Experienced in all stages of the development cycle for web projects from graphic design and features development to deployment and mantaining of cloud server infrastructure.

I would describe myself as flexible, responsible, open-minded, and willing to learn. I'm able to be entirely self-sufficient, however I am enthusiastic about being a part of a team, learning from stronger team memb ers and helping others to grow.

Skills

Well-versed in a rich set of **tools** from programming languages (ex. JS, C#), markup and styling languages (HTML, CSS, SASS), databases (MySQL, MS SQL) to source control (Git, GitHub, GitLab), CI/CD (Jenkins, Gitlab and Github actions), static code analysers (SonarQube) and cloud platforms (DigitalOcean).

Experience

Itransition Group Software Engineer

May 2022 - Present

Yerevan, Armenia

As a part of a team of full-stack developers, I worked on Data Analytics and Business Intelligence web solutions based on .Net platform, the main job of which was to transform client market/research data through ETL process to then deliver insights into complex data with different reporting engines.

Freelance Web Developer

September 2020 - May 2022

As a freelancer, I have been creating landing pages, personal blogs, and other websites for various clients (ex. music bands, artists, and fitness trainers) from concept and graphic design to implementation, deployment, and support. My purpose was to make content easy to add and update in the future with open-source or custom-made content management systems.

Belarusian State Philharmonic Society Orchestra artist September 2018 - May 2022 Minsk, Belarus

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science:

Computer Science and Software Engineering – 2024 Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics, Minsk

Bachelor of Music:

Performing Arts - 2019 Belarusian State Academy of Music, Minsk